A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Staff Subject Files, Kilolo Kijakazi FA1848
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Working Files and Ford Foundation Initiatives, 1987-2014; 1; 37.3 Cubic Feet
  - National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI), 1998-2014; 11
    Grant Numbers 1110-0125 and 1100-0697
    Grant 10901034, 2009 August 01-2011 January 31
    For a re-granting program to increase knowledge about the best ways to ensure economic security for population groups most reliant on the U.S. Social Security Program
    Grant 10900691, 2009 April 01-2010 March 31
    To educate policymakers, media, and the public on the need to improve benefit adequacy for low-wage workers while restoring financial solvency to the Social Security System
    Grant 10800148, 2007 October 01-2009 September 30
    General support for NASI's core activities to provide information on social insurance programs to the general public
    - What's Next for Social Security? Meeting, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Feedback from Retirement Security Grantees, 2011-2012 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - 19th Annual Conference, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Summer Academy Opening Remarks Notes, 2008 July 22 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW) Conference, Boston - Lifting Every Voice: Empowering Women of Color, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Testimony Before the Employee Retirement Income Security Act (ERISA) Advisory Council, 2010 June 30 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Social Security 75th Anniversary Forum Insight, 2007-2010 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Insight Social Security Webinar, 2010 June 17 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - June 22, Social Security Forum 75th Anniversary, 2006-2010 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Social Security Grants Program, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI) (1075-0822) - Social Security Convening (Notes and Meetings), 2007 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - 18th Annual Conference, Older and Out of Work: Jobs and Social Insurance for a Changing Economy, 2006 January 19-20 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - 21st Annual Conference, Social Insurance, Fiscal Responsibility, and Economic Growth, 2009 January 29-30 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Working File, Grant Number 1060-0860, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Working File, Grant Number 1050-0344, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Older and Out of Work: Jobs and Social Insurance for a Changing Economy, Grant 1045-1250, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - Working File, Grant Number 1020-1205, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - Social Security Brief (Publication), 1998-2010 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Fixing Social Security: Adequate Benefits, Adequate Financing, Virginia P. Reno and Joni Lavery, 2009 October (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Social Security: An Essential Asset and Insurance Protection for All, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Economic Crisis Fuels Support for Social Security: Americans' Views on Social Security, 2009 August (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 1, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 2, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 3, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 4, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 5, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 6, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 7, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 8, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 9, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 10, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 11, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 12, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 13, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 14, 2010 February 17; CD; This item was imaged from a CD in 2023 (Box 26)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance 15, 2010 February 17; CD (Box 26)
    - Working Files and Regranting Program Grant Information, 2007-2013 (Box 82, Folder 733-735, Box 83, Folder 736-739, Box 84, Folder 740)
      Grant Numbers 1110-0125, 1100-0697,
      National Academy of Social Insurance (10901034), 2009 August 01-2011 January 31
      National Academy of Social Insurance (10900691), 2009 April 01-2010 March 31
      National Academy of Social Insurance (10800148), 2007 October 01-2009 September 30
      National Academy of Social Insurance (10750822), 2007 May 01-2008 February 29
    - Strengthening the Web of Financial and Retirement Security for Today's Working Americans, 26th Annual Policy Research Conference, Washington, D.C., 2014 January 29-30 (Box 84, Folder 741)
    - Beyond the Bad Economy: Jobs, Retirement, Health and Social Insurance, Washington, D.C., 2010 January 21-22 (Box 84, Folder 742)
    - Awardee Convening, 2011-2012 (Box 84, Folder 743)
    - Medicare and Social Security in a Time of Budget Austerity, 25th Annual Policy Research Conference, Washington, D.C., 2013 January 31-February 1 (Box 84, Folder 744)
    - Addressing Benefit Adequacy with Social Security Solvency, Ford Foundation Summit, 2010 February (Box 84, Folder 745)
    - Social Insurance in a Market Economy: Obstacles and Opportunities, 24th Annual Policy Research Conference, Washington, D.C., 2012 January 26-27 (Box 85, Folder 746)
    - Meeting Today's Challenges in Social Security, Health Reform, and Unemployment, 23rd Annual Conference, Washington, D.C., 2011 January 27-28 (Box 85, Folder 747)
    - Employee Benefit Research Institute (EBRI) Data on Elderly Financial Position, 2009-2010 (Box 85, Folder 748)
    - Heritage Strategy to Undo Social Security, 2013 (Box 85, Folder 749)
    - Demystifying Social Security: Academy for Interns, 2010 July 22 (Box 85, Folder 750)
    - Social Security at 75: The Legacy and Vision Forum, 2010 June 22 (Box 85, Folder 751)
    - Social Security Academy for Interns: Don't Leave Washington Clueless about Social Security, 2009 July 30 (Box 85, Folder 752)
    - Social Security Grant-making: Sharing the Results, 2007 July 11 (Box 85, Folder 753-754)
    - Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 85, Folder 755)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED), 1995-2012; 12
    Biographical / Historical
    The Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment Initiative (SEED) was a 10-year, multi-million dollar national policy, practice and research program to develop, test and promote matched savings accounts and financial education for children. There were 10 small-scale pilot projects administered by local foundations, a project focused on Head Start Centers in Michigan, a project that partnered with the State of Oklahoma (SEED for Oklahoma Kids) to provide savings accounts to children at birth, work by the New America Foundation to advocate for legislation, and an Initiative on Financial Security at the Aspen Institute.
    Funding partners included the Charles and Helen Schwab Foundation, Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, Citi Foundation, Edwin Gould Foundation for Children, Evelyn and Walter Haas Jr. Fund, Ewing Marion Kauffman Foundation, The Ford Foundation, Jim Casey Youth Opportunity Initiative, Lumina Foundation for Education, MetLife Foundation, and the Richard and Rhoda Goldman Fund.
    - Policy Council Meeting, 2008 March 20 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Policy Council, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Meeting, 2005 June (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Grant Negotiations with Partners, 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Oakland Livingston Human Services Association (OLHSA) Sample Size Issues, 2005 April-May (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Oakland Livingston Human Services Association (OLHSA) Enrollment and Account Opening Issues, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Center for Social Development (CSD), Washington University in St. Louis Research Reports, 2006-2008 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Account Monitoring Reports for Center for Social Development (CSD) and University of Kansas School of Social Welfare, 2005-2009 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - University of Kansas Research Reports, 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) Reports and Publications, 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Initiative Report, 2009 October (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Financial Report, All Funders, 2009 January-June (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Initiative Report, 2009 April (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Financial Report, All Funders, 2008 January-June (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - Initiative Report, 2008 October (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - Initiative Report, 2008 April (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Financial Report, All Funders, 2007 July-December (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Initiative Report, 2007 October (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - Initiative Report, 2006 October (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - Semi-Annual Progress Report, 2006 April (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - Interim Report to Funders, 2005 July-December (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - Semi-Annual Progress Report, 2005 March (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) Semi-Annual Report to Funders, Semi-Annual Meeting Notes, and SEED Initiative and Partnership Progress Report, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - Site Progress Briefs Requested by Rick Williams, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - Policy Matrix, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - Conversations with Rick Williams - Notes and Progress Briefs, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 120)
    - Partner Meeting, 2009 April 7 (Box 15, Folder 121)
    - Partner Calls (Monthly), 2009 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - Partner Disputes, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids: The Impact Evaluation, Final Report Draft, Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Evaluation Plan, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, Center for Social Development (CSD), Initial Account Opening and Savings, Draft, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, Data Sharing Agreement, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Budget, Center for Social Development (CSD), 2008 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, 2009-2015 Budget, University of Kansas, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, 2009-2015 Budget, Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International, Remaining Work on Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) Oklahoma, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - Budget, Center for Enterprise Development (CFED), Beyond 2009 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - Research Advisory Council (RAC) November 15, 2011 Meeting at Ford (Box 15, Folder 133)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Research Advisory Council (RAC) Expansion, 2004-2011 (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Conference Calls, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Research Advisory Council (RAC) Meeting, 2010 April 22 (Box 16, Folder 136)
    - Research Advisory Council (RAC) Meeting, 2009 July 8 (Box 16, Folder 137)
    - Research Advisory Council (RAC) Meeting, 2008 October 21 (Box 16, Folder 138)
    - Research Advisory Council (RAC) Meeting, 2006 October (Box 16, Folder 139)
    - Research Advisory Council (RAC) Meeting, 2004 July 8 (Box 16, Folder 140)
    - Milestones and Timelines for September 2009-September 2010, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 141)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, Follow-up Survey Activities, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 142)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International, Timing of Wave 2 and Cost, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 143)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, Child Development Experts Discussions, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 144)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International, Sample Maintenance Activities Report, 2008 September (Box 16, Folder 145)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids: Baseline Analysis Draft Report, Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International and Kilolo's Comments, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 146)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Cognitive Interviewing Report and Conference Call Notes, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 147)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, Issues Associated with Assets and Liabilities for Survey, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - Data Collection, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 149)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Launch and Press Conference, 2008 June 3 (Box 17, Folder 150)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids, Universal Model Meeting in Oklahoma, 2006 July 18 (Box 17, Folder 151)
    - Universal Model Focus Groups, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 152)
    - Universal Model Matching Issues, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 153)
    - Universal Model Sampling and Statistical Power, 2006-2008 (Box 17, Folder 154)
    - Selection of Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International, Universal Policy Model and Research: Evaluation of Experiment, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 155)
    - Universal Policy Model and Research Evaluation of Experiment Request for Proposal, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 156)
    - Universal Model Site Selection, 2005 August 10 (Box 17, Folder 157)
    - Building Assets: An Impact Evaluation of the Michigan SEED Children's Savings Program, RTI International, 2009 November (Box 17, Folder 158)
    - Kilolo's Talking Points on Michigan Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED), 2009 (Box 17, Folder 159)
    - Preserving Michigan Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) Data for Trina Shanks, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 160)
    - For October 29, 2009 Conference Call with Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) Advisory Council to Resolve Disputes (Box 17, Folder 161)
    - Partner and Research Advisory Council (RAC) Comments on Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International Michigan Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) Impact Report, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 162)
    - Michigan Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) Synthesis Report, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 163)
    - A Process Study of the Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) Community Partners Initiaitive, RTI International and University of Kansas, 2006-2009 (Box 17, Folder 164)
    - Meeting with Wayne Holden, Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International, 2008 January 16 (Box 18, Folder 165)
    - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International's Involvement, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 166)
    - Communication with Ellen Marks, 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 167)
    - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International Quarterly Reports on SEED Activities, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 168)
    - Kilolo Kijakazi Site Visit to Research Triangle Institute (RTI) Raleigh Durham, 2008 January (Box 18, Folder 169)
    - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) International Headquarters Site Visit, 2008 March (Box 18, Folder 170)
    - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) and Michael Wiseman, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 171)
    - Issue of Data Sharing between Center for Social Development (CSD), University of Kansas (KU), and RTI Call, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 172)
    - Advisory Board Meeting, Denver, 2008 October 22 (Box 18, Folder 173)
    - Advisory Board Meeting, Philadelphia, 2008 April 10 (Box 18, Folder 174)
    - Policy Council (SPC) and Advisory Board (SAB) Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2007 February 6 (Box 18, Folder 175)
    - Advisory Board Meeting, 2006 March 6 (Box 18, Folder 176)
    - Advisory Board Meeting (Participated by Phone), 2006 October 17 (Box 18, Folder 177)
    - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008 October 22 (Box 18, Folder 178)
    - Advisory Board Semi-Annual Meeting, 2005 April 14 (Box 18, Folder 179)
    - Advisory Board Meeting on Expanded Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED), 2004 September 20 (Box 18, Folder 180)
    - State Policy Request for Proposals (RFP), 2005 (Box 18, Folder 181)
    - State Policy Meeting, 2008 October 24 (Box 18, Folder 182)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids: A Special Opportunity To Save for Your Child, Answers to Frequently Asked Questions, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 183)
      SEED publication
    - Semi-Annual Advisory Board Meeting, Philadelphia, 2008 April 9-11 (Box 18, Folder 184)
    - Semi-Annual Advisory Board Meeting, Puerto Rico, 2007 April 19 (Box 18, Folder 185)
    - Semi-Annual Advisory Board Meeting, St. Louis, 2007 October 17-19 (Box 19, Folder 186)
    - Semi-Annual Advisory Board Meeting, Arkansas, 2006 April 24-26 (Box 19, Folder 187)
    - Semi-Annual Advisory Board Meeting, Detroit, 2005 October (Box 19, Folder 188)
    - Policy Council, Second Convening, 2006 February 16 (Box 19, Folder 189)
    - Advisory Board Meeting, San Francisco, 2005 April 14 (Box 19, Folder 190)
    - Oakland Livingston Human Service Agency (OLHSA), Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) Michigan Impact Evaluation Follow-up, undated (Box 19, Folder 191)
    - Oakland Livingston Human Service Agency (OLHSA) Baseline Surveys and Field Representative Manual, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 192)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) Research Instrument, Impact Assessment Survey, Fall 2004 Baseline Instrument in English and Spanish, Center for Social Development at Washington University, University of Kansas School of Social Welfare (Box 19, Folder 193)
    - Oakland Livingston Human Service Agency (OLHSA) SEED Program Communications Materials Semi-Annual Meeting, Arkansas, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 194)
    - Kilolo Kijakazi and Corporation for Enterprise Development's (CFED) Guidelines for Site Visits, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 195)
    - Community Partner Performance Standards - Draft, 2006 April 21 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - Community Partners - Account Rollover Process Memo, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 197)
    - Shriver Center - Embezzlement Response, 2007 February (Box 19, Folder 198)
    - Delaware Sites - Recommendations for Moving Forward, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 199)
    - Oakland Livingston Human Service Agency (OLHSA), Pontiac, Michigan Sites, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 200)
    - Grant Renewals, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 201)
    - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) 2007-2009 Proposal and Comments, 2004-2007 (Box 20, Folder 202)
    - Center for Social Development (CSD), George Warren Brown School of Social Work, Washington University in St. Louis 2007-2009 Proposal Draft and Ford Questions and Concerns, 2007 May (Box 20, Folder 203)
    - New America Foundation (NAF) Proposal and Comments, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 204)
    - Kilolo Kijakazi and Rick Williams' Comments on SEED Proposals, 2007 May 6 (Box 20, Folder 205)
    - University of Kansas SEED 2007-2009 Research Proposal, 2007 May (Box 20, Folder 206)
    - Notes from Kids Account Hearing and Hill Event on America Saving for Personal Investment, Retirement, and Education (ASPIRE), 2005 May 26 (Box 20, Folder 207)
    - United States Senate Committee on Finance, Building Assets for Low-Income Families Hearing Testimony and Statements, 2005 April 28 (Box 20, Folder 208)
    - Individual Development Accounts (IDA) and Asset Building in the States, Center for Social Development (CSD), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 209)
      Ford Foundation Grant 1010-1821
    - Center for Social Development (CSD) State Policy Grant and Guide, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 210)
      Washington University (10101821), 2001 July 01-2003 June 30
      To build enhanced capacity at the state level to develop, fund and operate individual development account programs
    - Center for Social Development (CSD) Working Papers, 1995-2005 (Box 20, Folder 211)
      Draft Chapter: Building Assets Among African-American Males, Michale Sherraden
      Working Papers: Investment in Human Development as a Social Strategy, Sondra Beverly and Michael Sherraden, 1995
      Working Papers: Homeownership and its Impacts: Implications for Low-Income Families, Edward Scanlon, 1996
      Working Papers: What We Know About Effects of Asset Holding Implications for Research on Asset-Based Anti-Poverty Initiatives, Deborah Page-Adams and Michael Sherraden, 1996
      Working Papers: Effects of Assets on Attitudes and Behaviors: Advance Test of a Social Policy Proposal, Gautam N. Yadama and Michael Sherraden, 1995
      Working Papers: Education, Assets, and Intergenerational Well-Being: The Casse of Female Headed Families, Li-Chen Cheng and Deborah Page-Adams, 1996
      Working Papers: Home Mortgage Lending in St. Louis City: An Analysis of 1993 and 1994 Home Mortgage Disclosure Act Data, Edward Scanlon and Shirley Emerson, 1997
    - Center for Social Development (CSD) 529 Children's Savings Plan, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 212)
    - Center for Social Development (CSD) Endowment Working File, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 213)
    - Visit to Center for Social Development (CSD) by Kilolo Kijakazi and Frank DeGiovanni, 2005 April 21 (Box 21, Folder 214)
    - Center for Social Development (CSD) Conversation with Michael Sherraden Notes, 2005 March 11 (Box 21, Folder 215)
    - Washington University - Recommendation for Grant Actions (RGAs), 1996-2001 (Box 21, Folder 216)
    - Washington University Proposals for Fiscal Year 2003, 1997-2002 (Box 21, Folder 217)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids: The Impact Evaluation Review Draft for Research Advisory Council (RAC) Meeting, 2014 January 31 (Box 88, Folder 782)
    - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Cognitive Interviewing Report, 2007 May; CD (Box 88)
    - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids - Working File, 2010-2011 (Box 88, Folder 783)
      Grant Number 1100-0920
    - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) - Grant 1060-0724, 2008-2009 (Box 88, Folder 784)
      Research Triangle Institute (10600724), 2006 May 01-2010 July 31
      For an evaluation of a demonstration to determine the feasibility and potential impact of a universal children's savings account system in the United States
    - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids - Cost Overrun, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 785)
  - Convening of Social Security Experts, 2003-2005; 13
    - Information on Social Security, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 276)
      National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI) - Savings, Asset-Building and Social Security Seminar
    - Bob Rosenblatt's Summary, 2005 May (Box 29, Folder 277)
    - Transcript, 2004 May 5 (Box 29, Folder 278)
    - Attendees and Agenda, 2004 May 5 (Box 29, Folder 279)
    - Preparation Materials, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 280)